

## ISOON LAOHASOOT

Working as Software Developer with 3 years of professional working experience and 1 year for part time. I am passionate with programming because it's exciting and challenging for myself. Currently, I am interested to improve my programming skill with Node.js and Graphql.

#### **EDUCATION**

King Mongkut's Institute of Technology Ladkrabang. Graduated in 2015

• Bachelor of Information Technology

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## 2014 Part time Software Developer at Five Loop

I was working as a part time developer for fiveloop company with a php, codeigniter, sql. FIVELOOP is a start up to help programmer find a job and help company to find a good programmer and At that time I helped FIVELOOP to create a joblist website for programmer.

# 2015 - 2017 Junior Software Developer at Fiveloop

I decided to work at fiveloop becuase I think I like a startup culture and I can decide every thing about technology for create a software in this company, At that time I started the project called "Cerebro", its idea was scraping all programmer data from job list web or social media like a linkedin, github and then I collected it in our database for searching about jobs, and candidates, this software help the company to send a potential candidates to other company.

### 2017-2019 Senior Software Developer at Fiveloop

I use Node.js, React, MariaDB to make a software for my company called "Wisible", that is a sales automation software for team sales or anyone who need to track sales process and manage sales work flow like a salesforce but easy to use and easy to customize and this is the most proundly project because I choose tech stack called Appollo (Graphql), at that time I was lernining about this stack from zero. I expect it Helps my work to easier than older project.

#### 2019-2020 Senior Software Developer at ATvantage

I use Node.js, React lambda, dynamodb to build a platform called "FULLOOP". Actually, they have a old platform but It too old. They need me to build a new one follow the old project. The feature is as same as the old one but tech stack is new technology (React, Node, dynamo). This project is a platform for suvey and report. For this job I have lerned a lot about AWS Stack (EC2, Memcached, Lambda, DynamoDB, CloudFront, CloudFormation, CloudWatch) and lerned about ElasticSearch Kibana.

#### **SKILLS**

**Languages:** Native Fluency in both spoken and written in Thai, Fair command of English

Confident in JavaScript, Node.js, Apollo(grahpql), React, SQL, Mongo

**Skill**: Html CSS Node.JS SQL Mongo Java Python PHP (codeigniter) React AngularJS Nginx Docker Apollo Github